<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/faqs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/faqs/</guid><description>Q: I get undefined symbol: run or undefined symbol: cdiver or similar when I try to run a scan. What gives?
A: You probably forgot to re-run cmake (followed by make) after building the scanner you&amp;rsquo;re trying to run with.
Q: Is the detector parameterisation BuckFast in ColliderBit named after Andy Buckley?
A: No.
Q: Is Are Raklev&amp;rsquo;s first name really Åre?
A: No, that&amp;rsquo;s a ski resort.</description></item><item><title>Compiler Matrix</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/compiler_matrix/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/compiler_matrix/</guid><description>Below is a list of compilers compatible with GAMBIT and different backends and scanners.
ⓘ The backend and scanner entries refer to the form used in GAMBIT, i.e. after any patching or BOSSing applied by the GAMBIT build system. We have also tested various earlier compilers, but not in as much detail. Please let us know if you have information on presently untested combinations (marked with ?, or missing entirely).</description></item><item><title>Known Issues</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/known_issues/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/known_issues/</guid><description>ⓘ Please report any new unresolved issues here. Issue Description Error Python error: is a directory, cannot continue when linked to MPICH and executing via mpiexec/mpirun with &amp;gt;1 process In some rare cases, this error will occur when trying to run with multiple MPI processes after having compiled with MPI support via the MPICH libraries. As best we can tell, it is caused by a bug in either the MPICH libraries or some version of the Python runtime libraries.</description></item><item><title>Configuration Examples</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/configuration_examples/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/testbit/documentation/help/configuration_examples/</guid><description>ⓘ Instructions for configuring and compiling GAMBIT can be found in the original paper describing the code arXiv:1705.07908. ⚠ For building the entirety of GAMBIT without optimisation, at least 10 GB of RAM is required. The build can be completed with less RAM than this if enough modules are ditched when running cmake, with e.g. cmake -Ditch=&amp;ldquo;ColliderBit;DarkBit&amp;rdquo; .., etc. See arXiv:1705.07908 for further details of how to ditch components. For a list of commonly used cmake options, see the file CMAKE_FLAGS.</description></item></channel></rss>