<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community on</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/</link><description>Recent content in Community on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/code_of_conduct/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/code_of_conduct/</guid><description>As adopted 29.10.2020. In this document we summarise our shared understanding of what constitutes good collaborative behaviour, and how such behaviour should be actively promoted in the GAMBIT Community. The aim of this code is to foster a healthy collaboration environment for all members of our community. Regardless of personal characteristics, seniority, role or contributions within GAMBIT, all members of our community are expected to read this code, and follow it both in spirit and letter.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/contact/</guid><description>You can send an email to the GAMBIT community here.</description></item><item><title>Members</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/members/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/members/</guid><description>About the Community GAMBIT is developed by a growing community of theorists and experimentalists, including members of the ATLAS, Belle-II, CTA, DARWIN, Fermi-LAT, HESS, IceCube, LHCb, SHiP and XENON experiments, as well as developers of the public theory codes Capt'n General, DarkSUSY, DDCalc, FlexibleSUSY, HEPLike, gamLike, GM2Calc, IsaJet, nulike, SoftSUSY, SuperIso and Vevacious. ⚠ The GAMBIT Community has a Code of Conduct. Gallery Fruzsina Agocs Viktor Ananiev Peter Athron Csaba Balazs</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/publications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/publications/</guid><description>ⓘ A full list of GAMBIT publications and proceedings can be found here. Physics Analyses Cosmological constraints on decaying axion-like particles: a global analysis, arXiv:2205.13549.
Thermal WIMPs and the Scale of New Physics: Global Fits of Dirac Dark Matter Effective Field Theories, Eur.Phys.J.C 81 (2021) 11, 992, arXiv:2106.02056.
Supplementary data, including samples: Strengthening the bound on the mass of the lightest neutrino with terrestrial and cosmological experiments, Phys.Rev.D 103 (2021) 12, 123508, arXiv:2009.</description></item><item><title>Talks</title><link>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/talks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://rc1242rc.github.io/community/talks/</guid><description>Here you can find some slides of a few selected talks about GAMBIT.
ⓘ More can be found on individual members' personal websites. SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal Fits of Dirac Dark Matter Effective Field TheoriesDateMarch 2022LocationCarleton University, Ottawa, CanadaReasonSeminar: Particle SeminarLinkLinkSpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the scale of new physicsDateDecember 2021LocationKing's College London, UKReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the Scale of New PhysicsDateAugust 2021LocationIllinois (online)ReasonConference: COSMO'21LinkLinkSpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal study of effective Higgs portal dark matter models using GAMBITDateDecember 2019LocationSydneyReasonConference: TeVPA (2019)LinkLinkSpeakerJanina RenkTitleCosmoBit: Towards Simultaneous Global Fits of Particle Physics and CosmologyDateSeptember 2019LocationAachen, GermanyReasonConference: Cosmo19LinkLinkSpeakerAndrew FowlieTitleCombined collider constraints on neutralinos and charginosDateAugust 2019LocationWeihai, ChinaReasonWorkshop: Tenth Weihai New Physics Meeting LinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleDark matter interpretation with global fitsDateAugust 2019LocationSeattleReasonWorkshop: Dark Matter @ LHC 2019LinkLinkSpeakerPeter AthronTitleNew Physics Interpretations with GAMBITDateJuly 2019LocationGhent, BelgiumReasonConference: EPS-HEPLinkLinkSpeakerPat ScottTitleSearches for dark matter with GAMBITDateJuly 2019LocationBrisbane, AustraliaReasonConference: Astronomical Society of Australia Annual Scientific MeetingLinkLinkSpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal study of effective Higgs portal dark matter models using GAMBITDateJuly 2019LocationGhent, BelgiumReasonConference: EPS-HEP 2019LinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleGlobal fits of neutrino and dark matter models with GAMBITDateJune 2019LocationMPIK Heidelberg, GermanyReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleA global fit of the type-I seesaw mechanismDateJune 2019LocationImperial College London, UKReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerCsaba BalazsTitleThe status of dark matterDateJune 2019LocationValencia, SpainReasonConference: Invisibles 2019LinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleStatus of global SUSY fitsDateMay 2019LocationCorpus Christi, Texas, USReasonConference: SUSY 2019LinkLinkSpeakerPat ScottTitleStatus of non-supersymmetric dark matter theories with GAMBITDateMay 2019LocationPoznan, PolandReasonConference: PRACEDays 2019, EuroHPC SummitLinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleInvestigating supersymmetry with GAMBITDateMay 2019LocationPoznanReasonConference: PRACEdays 2019LinkLinkSpeakerPat ScottTitleStatus of non-supersymmetric models with GAMBITDateApril 2019LocationObergurgl, AustriaReasonConference: ALPS (Alpine LHC Summit)LinkLinkSpeakerBen FarmerTitleStatus of supersymmetric models with GAMBITDateApril 2019LocationObergurgl, AustriaReasonConference: ALPS (Alpine LHC Summit)LinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleGlobal fits on BSM modelsDateMarch 2019LocationMonash University, AustraliaReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleExploring light SUSY with GAMBITDateMarch 2019LocationLa ThuileReasonConference: Moriond QCD 2019LinkLinkSpeakerSebastian HoofTitleAxion Global Fits with Peccei-Quinn Symmetry Breaking Before Inflation using GAMBITDateOctober 2018LocationHamburg, GermanyReasonConference: DESY Theory WorkshopLinkLinkSpeakerBen FarmerTitleGlobal fits in “Beyond the Standard Model” physicsDateOctober 2018LocationDarmstadt, GermanyReasonConference: ISNET-6LinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleCombined collider constraints on neutralinos and charginos with GAMBITDateOctober 2018LocationImperial College LondonReasonSeminar: 3-PAC seminarLinkLinkSpeakerCsaba BalazsTitleSUSY according to GAMBITDateJuly 2018LocationBarcelonaReasonConference: SUSY 2018LinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleMSSM global fits with GAMBITDateJuly 2018LocationSeoulReasonConference: ICHEP 2018LinkLinkSpeakerBen FarmerTitleCalculating p-values in Beyond-the-Standard-Model global fitsDateJune 2018LocationMonash University, Melbourne, AustraliaReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleChasing SUSY through parameter spaceDateJune 2018LocationAachenReasonSeminarLinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleSterile Neutrinos in GAMBITDateMay 2018LocationStavanger, NorwayReasonWorkshop: N-PACT Meeting 2018LinkLinkSpeakerTomas GonzaloTitlePreviously on GAMBIT.</description></item></channel></rss>